Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sheet Music (Irish), 1817-1995, 191937
  - I, 336034
    - Irish Washerwoman, The, 1907; 192703 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Irish Washerwoman, The (2), 1954; 192702 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Irish Weavin' Song, 1905; 192701 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Irish Wedding, The, undated; 192700 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Irish Wedding Song, The, 1995; 192699 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Irishman's Greeting to America, The, 1853; 192698 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Irishman's Shanty, The, 1859; 192697 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Is that Mr. Reilly?, 1883; 192696 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Is that You, O'Reilly?, 1915; 192695 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Is Your Mother in Molly Malone?, 1903; 192694 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Island of Green, The, 1907; 192693 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Isle O'Dreams, 1912; 192692 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Isle of Innisfree, The, 1950; 192691 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Isle that's Crown'd with Shamrock, The, 1884; 192690 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - It May Be Far to Tipperary, It's a Longer Way to Tennessee, 1914; 192689 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - It Takes a Great Big Irish Heart to Sing an Irish Song, 1915; 192688 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - It Takes the Irish to Beat the Dutch, 1903; 192687 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - It's a Great Day for the Irish, 1940; 192686 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - It's a Long, Long Way to Tipperary, 1912; 192685 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - It's a Rocky Road to Dublin, 1913; 192684 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - It's My Old High Hat, 1902; 192683 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - It's Nice to be Nice to a Nice Little Girl like You, 1911; 192682 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - It's Not Your Nationality, 1916; 192681 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - It's the Irish in Me, 1951; 192680 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - It's the Irish in Your Eye, It's the Irish in Your Smile, 1916; 192679 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - It's the land of the Shillelah for me, 1922; 192678 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - It's the Music in the Irish, 1924; 192677 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - It's the Same Old Shillelagh, 1940; 192676 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - It's the Shamrock that Grows by my Door, 1914; 192675 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - It's the Three Leaves of Shamrock, 1915; 192674 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - I've Got the River Shannon Blues, 1922; 192673 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - I've Worked Eight Hours this Day, undated; 192672 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - J, 336033
    - Jaunting Car, The, 1923; 192671 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair, 1939; 192670 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Jennie, the Flower of Kildare, 1873; 192669 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Jerry, 1919; 192668 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - John James O'Reilly, 1921; 192667 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - John Maloney's Sweetheart, 1890; 192666 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Johnny Doughboy Found a Rose in Ireland!, 1942; 192665 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Johnny Keane's Courtship, 1865; 192664 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Joys of an Irish Dance, The, 1906; 192663 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Juc of a Punch, The, 1897; 192662 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Judge He's-A-Irish-Too!, The, 1912; 192661 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Judy, 1921; 192660 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Just a Bit of Irish Lace, 1922; 192659 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Just a Little Bit of Green, 1913; 192658 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Just a Plain Little Irish Girl, 1910; 192657 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Just Mention the Old Emerald Isle, 1928; 192656 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Just Sing a Song for Ireland, 1898; 192655 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - K, 336032
    - Kate Connor, undated; 192654 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Kate Kearney, 1904, nd; 192653 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Kate Killarney, 1910; 192652 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Kate O'Brien, undated; 192651 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Kate O'Donoghue, 1897; 192650 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Kate O'Shane, undated; 192649 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Kathleen, 1920; 192648 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Kathleen (2), 1921; 192647 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Kathleen Aroon, nd, 1910; 192646 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Kathleen Is Gone, undated; 192645 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Kathleen Is Waiting For Me, 1888; 192644 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Kathleen Mavourneen, 1909, 1935, 1942, nd; 192643 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Kathleen Mavourneen (2), 1919; 192642 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Kathleen Mavourneen (3), undated; 192641 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Kathleen My Rose, 1917; 192640 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Kathleen O'Moore, undated; 192639 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Kathleen, the Rose of My Heart, 1874; 192638 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Katie, 1906; 192637 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Katie's Eyes Are Irish, 1904; 192636 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Katy Darling's Farewell to Dermot, 1852; 192635 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Katy Mahone, 1894; 192634 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Keep the Horseshoe, 1880; 192633 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Kelly, I'm Glad to See You Back, 1919; 192632 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Kelly, the Carman, 1898; 192631 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Kellys Are At It Again, The, 1913; 192630 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Kelly's Gone to Kingdom Come, 1910; 192629 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Kelly's Masquerade Ball, 1892; 192628 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Kerry Dance, The, 1941; 192627 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Kerry Mills Barn Dance, 1908; 192626 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Kilcoy Schottische, The, undated; 192625 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Kilkenny, 1911, 1912; 192624 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Killaloe, undated; 192623 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Killaloo, 1915; 192622 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Killarney, [circa 1915]; 192621 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Killarney (2), nd, 1940; 192620 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Killarney Colleen, 1917; 192619 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Killarney Kate, 1924; 192618 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Killarney, My Home O'er the Sea, 1908, 1911; 192617 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Killarney, the Blarney, and You, 1924; 192616 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Killbarney Trip to Paris, The, undated; 192615 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Kind of a Girl I Mean, The, 1918; 192614 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - King Finnigan, 1901; 192613 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - King Mickey Malone, 1910; 192612 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Kitty, 1923; 192611 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Kitty Donohue, 1921; 192610 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Kitty Dooley, 1903; 192609 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Kitty O'Neil, 1904; 192608 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Kitty Tyrrell, undated; 192607 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - K-K-K-Katy, 1918; 192606 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Knights of St. Patrick, The, 1878; 192605 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Kosher Kitty Kelly, 1925; 192604 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - L, 336031
    - Laddie Buck, 1908; 192603 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Laddie Buck of Mine, 1920; 192602 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Lads Who Live in Ireland, The, 1864; 192601 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lament of the Irish Emigrant, The, 1843; 192600 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Lament of the Irish Lover, 1847; 192599 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Land O'Romance, The, 1922; 192598 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lannagin's Shillalah, 1941; 192597 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Larry Moore, 1890; 192596 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lass from the County Mayo, The, 1913; 192595 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lass I Love, The, 1900; 192594 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lass of Limerick Town, The, 1917; 192593 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Lass that I Loved in Killarney, The, 1913; 192592 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Last Rose of Summer, The, 1925; 192591 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Last Sod of Turf, The, 1918; 192590 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Laughing Irish Eyes, 1936; 192589 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Learn to Smile ( from The O'Brien Girl ), 1921; 192588 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Leaves of the Shamrock, The, 1920; 192587 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Legacy, The ( Part III of Ireland ), undated; 192586 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Legend of the Maguire, The, 1904; 192585 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Leprehaun, The, 1935; 192584 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Let Me Glance At Dear Old Ireland Once Again, 1911; 192583 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Let the Farmer Praise His Grounds, 1916; 192582 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Let the Rest of the World Go By, 1919; 192581 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Let's Help the Irish Now, 1919; 192580 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Lights of Bantry Bay, The, 1911; 192579 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Limerick Girls, 1902; 192578 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Listen to that Irish Ragtime Band, 1912; 192577 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Little American Boy, 1943; 192576 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Little Annie Rooney, nd, 1890, 1925; 192575 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Little Colleen I Love, The, 1908; 192574 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Little Galway Cloak, The, 1906; 192573 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Little Homes of Ireland, The, 1947; 192572 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Little Irish Dance, 1949; 192571 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Little Irish Girl, The, 1903; 192570 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Little Irish Home, 1937; 192569 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Little Irish Rose, 1928; 192568 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Little Katie Dooley is My Wife Now, 1890; 192567 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Little Maggie Ann, 1879; 192566 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Little Maggie Brady, 1911; 192565 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Little Maggie Magee, 1891; 192564 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Little Miss Killarney, 1913; 192563 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Little Red Lark, The, undated; 192562 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Little Skillet Pot, The, 1963; 192561 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Little Tommy Murphy, 1900; 192560 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Little Town in the Ould County Down, 1920; 192559 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Little Widow Dunn, The, 1879; 192558 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Live in My Heart and Pay No Rent, 1902; 192557 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Londonderry Air, 1928; 192556 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Londonderry Air (2), 1935; 192555 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Look What My Boy Got in France, 1918; 192554 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Love Dreams, 1923; 192553 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Love of the Shamrock, The, 1879; 192552 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Lovely Katie, 1914; 192551 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Love's Old Sweet Song, c. 1914; 192550 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Low Back'd Car, The, 1846; 192549 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Luck O' the Road, 1950; 192548 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - M, 336030
    - Mac O-Macorkity, 1877; 192547 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Macnamara's Band, 1917; 192546 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Macushla, 1910; 192545 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Mademoiselle O'Toole, 1911; 192544 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Maggie McGlynn, 1896; 192543 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Maggie Murphy's Home, 1890; 192542 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Maggie O'Reilly, 1903; 192541 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Maggie, Darling, Now Good Bye, 1872; 192540 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Maguires, The, 1881; 192539 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Major O'Flaherty, 1893; 192538 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Mamie Brady's the girl for me, 1899; 192537 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Man Know Thyself, c. 1900; 192536 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Mar-an-da, 1908; 192535 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Márie Ann, 1910; 192534 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Martyrs of Ireland, The, 1916; 192533 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Mary, 1918; 192532 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Mary Ann, 1904; 192531 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Mary Ann O'Sann, 1915; 192530 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Mary Ellen, 1903; 192529 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Mary Kelly's Beau, 1880; 192528 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Mary O'Brien, 1921; 192527 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Mary Regan, 1919; 192526 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Mary Tracy 'How would you like to become a Casey?', 1921; 192525 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - McAlheeny's Cake Walk, 1899; 192524 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - McCarthy in Picardy, 1918; 192523 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - McCormick the Masher, McNeil Chord System, 1879; 192522 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - McNulty's Café, 1892; 192521 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Me Little Dudeen, 1913; 192520 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Meet Me In Rose Time Rosie, 1908; 192519 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Meet Me Sweet Kathleen in Honeysuckle Time, 1906; 192518 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Meet Mister Callaghan, 1952; 192517 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Meeting of the Waters, The, undated; 192516 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Message of a Dying Engineer, The, 1908, 1913; 192515 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Michael McGinnity, 1904; 192514 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Mick McGilligan's Ball, 1948; 192513 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Mickey, 1943; 192512 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Mickey Donohue, 1923; 192511 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mickey O'Neil, 1921; 192510 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Micky, Midnight Sons, The, 1944; 192509 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mike, 1926; 192508 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mike Doolin's Jaunting Car, 1905; 192507 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mike McCarty's Wake, 1894; 192506 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Milk Maid of Tyrone, The, 1888; 192505 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Minni-Ha-Ha-Donohue, 1908; 192504 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Minstrel Boy, The, undated; 192503 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Minstrel of Clare, The, Minstrel Show Guide, 1896; 192502 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Miss Katy Donahue, 1909; 192501 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Miss Killarney, 1910; 192500 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Miss Mary, 1905; 192499 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Miss Molly O'Moore, 1930; 192498 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Miss O'Leary's Irish Fruit Cake, 1952; 192497 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Mister Dooley, 1902; 192496 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Mister Gallagher and Mister Shean, 1922; 192495 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Mister Moon and Turn Off the Light, 1910; 192494 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Mister Pat O'Hare, 1910; 192493 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mollie Casey, 1897; 192492 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Mollie Darling, 1871; 192491 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Mollie the Pride of Mayo, 1884; 192490 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Mollie Vaughn, 1925; 192489 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Molloy, My Boy, 1946; 192488 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Molly Dear, It's You I'm After, 1915; 192487 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Molly Malone, 1909, 1919, 1927; 192486 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Molly McGee, 1916; 192485 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Molly McGinnity, You're My Affinity, 1907; 192484 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Molly Melone, 1957; 192483 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Molly Me Own, 1916; 192482 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Molly O, 1921; 192481 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Molly O'Halloran, 1904; 192480 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Molly O'Morgan, undated; 192479 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Molly on the Shore, 1939; 192478 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Molly O'Reilly, 1948; 192477 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Molly O'Rourke, 1948; 192476 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Molly O'Shaughnessey, 1912; 192475 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 'Mong the Green Irish Hills, 1908; 192474 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Moonlight, 1921; 192473 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Mother in Ireland, 1922, 1923; 192472 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Mother Machree, 1910; 192471 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Mother Mavourneen, 1923; 192470 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Mother O'Me, 1917; 192469 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Mother O'Mine, 1914; 192468 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Mountains o'Mourne, The, undated; 192467 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Mr. Doolin' Stop Your Foolin', 1899; 192466 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Mr. Mulcahey Esquire, 1885; 192465 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Mr. Mulligan and Mr. Garrity, 1925; 192464 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Delaney of Newport, 1903; 192463 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. O'Harahan, 1905; 192462 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - M'self, 1922; 192461 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Muldoon, the Solid Man, 1874; 192460 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Muldoon's Big Bassoon, 1919; 192459 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Mulligan Guard, The, 1873; 192458 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Murphy's Head, 1892; 192457 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Mush, Mush, Mush, Tural-I-Addy, undated; 192456 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Musical Micheal Magan, 1916; 192455 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - My Barney Lies Over the Ocean, 1919; 192454 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - My Beautiful Irish Maid, 1894; 192453 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - My Beautiful Old Land, 1867; 192452 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - My Bernadine, 1905; 192451 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - My Charming Irish Lady, 1904; 192450 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - My Daddy's Auld Dudeen, 1911; 192449 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - My Dark Rosaleen, 1897; 192448 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - My Dear Irish Mother Who's Waiting For Me, 1920; 192447 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - My Dear Little Irish Girl, 1907; 192446 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - My Dublin Mary, 1910; 192445 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - My Fair Kathleen Ashtore, 1918; 192444 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - My First Love Was Irish, 1946; 192443 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - My Galway Rose, 1921; 192442 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - My Girl's An Irish Girl, 1947; 192441 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - My Heart Is Irish, 1954; 192440 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - My Heart Is With You Ireland, 1921; 192439 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - My Heart Tells Me, 1943; 192438 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - My Heart was in Old Ireland that Eve, 1900; 192437 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - My Heart's in Old Kilkenny, 1914; 192436 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - My Heart's in Old Killarney, 1936; 192435 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - My Heart's in Tipperary, 1915; 192434 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - My Heart's Tonight in Erin, 1914; 192433 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - My Home Near Killarney, 1935; 192432 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - My Irish American Rose, 1918; 192431 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - My Irish Caruso, 1909; 192430 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - My Irish Cinderella, 1917; 192429 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - My Irish Colleen, 1912; 192428 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - My Irish Colleen (2), 1917; 192427 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - My Irish Daisy, 1905; 192426 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - My Irish Dream Girl, 1914; 192425 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - My Irish Fluffy Ruffles, 1907; 192424 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - My Irish Girl, 1911; 192423 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - My Irish Girl (2), 1906; 192422 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - My Irish Girlie, 1909; 192421 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - My Irish Jaunting Car, 1952; 192420 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - My Irish Maid, 1905; 192419 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - My Irish Maid (2), 1907; 192418 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - My Irish Molly O, 1905; 192417 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - My Irish Mother, 1939; 192416 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - My Irish Paradise, 1929; 192415 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - My Irish Prairie Queen, 1909; 192414 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - My Irish Rosary, 1923; 192413 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - My Irish Rose, 1906; 192412 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - My Irish Rosie, 1906; 192411 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - My Kathleen, 1915; 192410 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - My Kathleen (2), 1947; 192409 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - My Kathleen's Gone Over the Sea, 1887; 192408 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - My Kilkenny Home, 1920; 192407 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - My Killarney Rose, 1911; 192406 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - My Killarney Rose (2), 1916; 192405 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - My Lagan Love, 1905; 192404 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - My Land, 1910; 192403 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - My Lass from the Land of the Shamrock, 1906; 192402 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - My Little Blarney Stone, 1908; 192401 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - My Little China Doll, 1917; 192400 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - My Little Cottage Home in Sweet Killarney, 1917; 192399 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - My Little Irish Canary, 1904; 192398 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - My Mother's Rosary, 1915; 192397 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - My Mother's Wedding Ring, 1917; 192396 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - My Name Is Kelly, nd, 1919; 192395 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - My Name Is Paddy Leary, 1916; 192394 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - My Nelly's Blue Eyes, 1947; 192393 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - My Own Colleen, 1896; 192392 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - My Own Dear Irish Queen, 1903; 192391 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - My Own Home Town In Ireland, 1915; 192390 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - My Pal Flanagan, 1930; 192389 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - My Pretty Colleen, 1907; 192388 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - My Rose of Erin's Isle, 1916; 192387 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - My Rose of Old Kildare, 1912; 192386 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - My Rose of Tipperary, 1915; 192385 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - My Sweet Colleen, 1909; 192384 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - My Sweet Derry Rose, 1913; 192383 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - My Sweetheart from Old Donegal, 1916; 192382 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - My Sweet Liberty Queen, 1915; 192381 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - My Sweet Little Colleen, 1915; 192380 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - My Wild Irish Rose, 1899, 1961; 192379 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - My Wild Irish Rose of Killarney, 1906; 192378 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - N, 334240
    - Nancy, 1924; 192377 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Nancy Clancy, 1946; 192376 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Nellie Kelly I Love You, 1922; 192375 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Never Let Yourself Forget That You Are Irish Too, 1915; 192374 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Never Take the Horseshoe from the Door, 1880; 192373 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Ninepenny Fidil, The, 1904; 192372 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Noel D'Irlande, undated; 192371 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - No Irish Need Apply, 1863; 192370 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - No One Knew O'Grady, 1898; 192369 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - No One Knows, 1913; 192368 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Norah-Floradora, undated; 192367 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Nora Kildare, undated; 192366 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Nora Machree, undated; 192365 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Nora Malone, 1909; 192364 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Norah McNamara, 1908; 192363 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Norah McShane, undated; 192362 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Nora, My Irish Queen, 1911; 192361 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Nora, My Irish Rose, 1906; 192360 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Nora O'Neal, 1866; 192359 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Noreen, 1913; 192358 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - O, 334239
    - O'Brien, 1910; 192357 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - O'Brien Has No Place to Go, 1908; 192356 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - O'Brien is Looking For You, 1917; 192355 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - O'Brien is tryin' to learn to talk Hawaiian, 1916; 192354 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Och, Girls Dear, 1916; 192353 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - O Erin! Remember Thy Glorious Past, 1921; 192352 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Off to Philadelphia, undated; 192351 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Officer Flaherty Whistles a Tune, 1938; 192350 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Officer Kelly, 1924; 192349 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Oft in the Stilly Night, undated; 192348 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Oh Bay of Dublin!, undated; 192347 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Oh, Did You Ne'er Hear of the Blarney, 1916; 192346 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Oh! Did You Not Hear of Kate Kearney, 1916; 192345 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Oh God! Set Old Ireland Free!, 1917; 192344 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Oh, He Promises, 1880; 192343 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Oh! How He Can Sing An Irish Song, 1914; 192342 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Oh! Molly Bawn Why Leave Me Pining, undated; 192341 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Oh! Paddy Dear, 1916; 192340 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Oh! Really O'Reilly!, 1945; 192339 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Oh! Steer My Bark to Erin's Isle, undated; 192338 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Oh! The Moment Was Sad, 1916; 192337 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Old Boreen, The, 1915; 192336 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Old Country, The, 1952; 192335 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Old Erin, the Home of my Heart, 1878; 192334 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Old Erin, the Shamrock and You, 1914; 192333 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Old Fashioned Irish Girl, 1924; 192332 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Old Green Isle, The, 1903; 192331 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Old Ireland, 1925; 192330 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Old Ireland You're My Darlin', 1865; 192329 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Old Ireland's Free and Calling Me, 1922; 192328 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Old Irish Sweetheart of Mine, 1933; 192327 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - O'Malley's Tango, 1956; 192326 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - O Mrs. O'Flarity, what did you mean by that, 1892; 192325 (Box 31, Folder 12)